[Applause]
[Music]
who recently received the highest award
again we have a lot of overachievers in
this room of the solomonic gift the
knight grand cross of the imperial order
of the star of honor of ethiopia
for his lifetime achievements in
community services
good evening
to all practice and ladies and gentlemen
dr carl a robson by his act of kindness
has appealed to our collective
conscience to do good for others
but the nobility and courage of his
profession he has enabled many
to live healthier lives as a
self-appointed ambassador for cleveland
he has enabled many therapists to come
to cleveland and make
it their home away from home i hope
mayor bruce is listening that means more
voters in cleveland
i do mean a personal honor to be given
the opportunity to introduce to you dr
robson whom i have known for four
decades although i don't exactly know
how i can do that in 90 seconds
thirdly i will just post my
total introduction on w w dot
i'm done
no just kidding
the trucking virgin is dr robson is
being inducted by cihf this evening in
recognition of his selfless deportment
of their own model who has endeared
himself to our community and the work
that large as an inspiring and selfless
humanitarian and medical doctor who has
made significant and positive difference
in the health and lives of considerable
number of minorities immigrant women men
and children who quickly run home and
for doing his part doing his part to
make cleveland a welcoming and
culturally rich city we honor this loyal
and proud third generation scottish
american who has demonstrated love for
ethiopian ethiopians and multicultural
coexistence as well for his unwavering
civic responsibilities and successful
leadership and many core foundations
projects carl we are in every way worthy
of the honor to be conferred upon you
you all rejoice in the recognition
that's been upgraded to you by cihf this
evening your induction to this honor is
an inspiring manifestation of the
highest community in which you are in
this community congratulations i present
to you my dear friend dr karl rauschen
to be inducted into cih the cleveland
international hall of fame thank you
[Music]
and thank you again
this was an unexpected honor for me um
you see i'm not quite the same as other
members of the ethiopian community and i
appreciate that they have
adopted me in 100 percent and it's been
it's been a great experience the past 40
years since my mother first
twisted my arm to go to ethiopia i was
reluctant to
go once i got there i just couldn't
believe the country the the wonderful
people the
the
wonderful terrain the scenery the
history i was uh instantly hooked
and i've been
in ethiopia in that sense ever ever
since
uh doing uh working with other good
friends of mine like the cleveland i've
met here in town and
our board
of
what we call mentally hall foundation
germapholeca and herb resnick
over the years
we've
done a number of
helpful projects
and it's been
with the help of everybody else
i certainly
need to spread this around i'm not the
i'm not
the big guy in this situation i don't
think
but mainly i'd really like to uh
to mention my wife
tonight i don't know if she made it here
yet
um sinai schiffer oh
we've been married for 30 years
and she's really been the
the backbone of my ethiopianism i mean
she's the one who knows the culture the
language
and so i rely on her
so much
and
what we've what we've been doing is just
trying to
help the community others
people in ethiopia
and
we'll continue to do the same
for years to come
and i again
thank you all for this great honor
and
have a good evening
[Applause]